<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Regolith – Policy and Process</title>
    <link>https://kgilmer.github.io/r13-dev-site/docs/policy-and-process/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Policy and Process on Regolith</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://kgilmer.github.io/r13-dev-site/docs/policy-and-process/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Privacy</title>
      <link>https://kgilmer.github.io/r13-dev-site/docs/policy-and-process/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kgilmer.github.io/r13-dev-site/docs/policy-and-process/privacy/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Policy and Process</title>
      <link>https://kgilmer.github.io/r13-dev-site/docs/policy-and-process/contributions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kgilmer.github.io/r13-dev-site/docs/policy-and-process/contributions/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        

&lt;div class=&#34;pageinfo pageinfo-primary&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These basic sample guidelines assume that your Docsy site is deployed using Netlify and your files are stored in GitHub. You can use the guidelines &amp;ldquo;as is&amp;rdquo; or adapt them with your own instructions: for example, other deployment options, information about your doc project&#39;s file structure, project-specific review guidelines, versioning guidelines, or any other information your users might find useful when updating your site. &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/kubeflow/website/blob/master/README.md&#34;&gt;Kubeflow&lt;/a&gt; has a great example.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don&#39;t forget to link to your own doc repo rather than our example site! Also make sure users can find these guidelines from your doc repo README: either add them there and link to them from this page, add them here and link to them from the README, or include them in both locations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We use &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt; to format and generate our website, the
&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/google/docsy&#34;&gt;Docsy&lt;/a&gt; theme for styling and site structure,
and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.netlify.com/&#34;&gt;Netlify&lt;/a&gt; to manage the deployment of the site.
Hugo is an open-source static site generator that provides us with templates,
content organisation in a standard directory structure, and a website generation
engine. You write the pages in Markdown (or HTML if you want), and Hugo wraps them up into a website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All submissions, including submissions by project members, require review. We
use GitHub pull requests for this purpose. Consult
&lt;a href=&#34;https://help.github.com/articles/about-pull-requests/&#34;&gt;GitHub Help&lt;/a&gt; for more
information on using pull requests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;quick-start-with-netlify&#34;&gt;Quick start with Netlify&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here&#39;s a quick guide to updating the docs. It assumes you&#39;re familiar with the
GitHub workflow and you&#39;re happy to use the automated preview of your doc
updates:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fork the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/google/docsy-example&#34;&gt;Regolith Linux repo&lt;/a&gt; on GitHub.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make your changes and send a pull request (PR).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you&#39;re not yet ready for a review, add &amp;ldquo;WIP&amp;rdquo; to the PR name to indicate
it&#39;s a work in progress. (&lt;strong&gt;Don&#39;t&lt;/strong&gt; add the Hugo property
&amp;ldquo;draft = true&amp;rdquo; to the page front matter, because that prevents the
auto-deployment of the content preview described in the next point.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wait for the automated PR workflow to do some checks. When it&#39;s ready,
you should see a comment like this: &lt;strong&gt;deploy/netlify — Deploy preview ready!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;Details&lt;/strong&gt; to the right of &amp;ldquo;Deploy preview ready&amp;rdquo; to see a preview
of your updates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continue updating your doc and pushing your changes until you&#39;re happy with
the content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When you&#39;re ready for a review, add a comment to the PR, and remove any
&amp;ldquo;WIP&amp;rdquo; markers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;updating-a-single-page&#34;&gt;Updating a single page&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&#39;ve just spotted something you&#39;d like to change while using the docs, Docsy has a shortcut for you:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;Edit this page&lt;/strong&gt; in the top right hand corner of the page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you don&#39;t already have an up to date fork of the project repo, you are prompted to get one - click &lt;strong&gt;Fork this repository and propose changes&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;Update your Fork&lt;/strong&gt; to get an up to date version of the project to edit. The appropriate page in your fork is displayed in edit mode.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Follow the rest of the &lt;a href=&#34;#quick-start-with-netlify&#34;&gt;Quick start with Netlify&lt;/a&gt; process above to make, preview, and propose your changes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;previewing-your-changes-locally&#34;&gt;Previewing your changes locally&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to run your own local Hugo server to preview your changes as you work:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Follow the instructions in &lt;a href=&#34;https://kgilmer.github.io/r13-dev-site/docs/getting-started&#34;&gt;Getting started&lt;/a&gt; to install Hugo and any other tools you need. You&#39;ll need at least &lt;strong&gt;Hugo version 0.45&lt;/strong&gt; (we recommend using the most recent available version), and it must be the &lt;strong&gt;extended&lt;/strong&gt; version, which supports SCSS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fork the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/google/docsy-example&#34;&gt;Regolith Linux repo&lt;/a&gt; repo into your own project, then create a local copy using &lt;code&gt;git clone&lt;/code&gt;. Don’t forget to use &lt;code&gt;--recurse-submodules&lt;/code&gt; or you won’t pull down some of the code you need to generate a working site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;git clone --recurse-submodules --depth 1 https://github.com/google/docsy-example.git
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Run &lt;code&gt;hugo server&lt;/code&gt; in the site root directory. By default your site will be available at http://localhost:1313/. Now that you&#39;re serving your site locally, Hugo will watch for changes to the content and automatically refresh your site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Continue with the usual GitHub workflow to edit files, commit them, push the
changes up to your fork, and create a pull request.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;creating-an-issue&#34;&gt;Creating an issue&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&#39;ve found a problem in the docs, but you&#39;re not sure how to fix it yourself, please create an issue in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/google/docsy-example/issues&#34;&gt;Regolith Linux repo&lt;/a&gt;. You can also create an issue about a specific page by clicking the &lt;strong&gt;Create Issue&lt;/strong&gt; button in the top right hand corner of the page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;useful-resources&#34;&gt;Useful resources&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[Docsy user guide](wherever it goes): All about Docsy, including how it manages navigation, look and feel, and multi-language support.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/documentation/&#34;&gt;Hugo documentation&lt;/a&gt;: Comprehensive reference for Hugo.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://guides.github.com/activities/hello-world/&#34;&gt;Github Hello World!&lt;/a&gt;: A basic introduction to GitHub concepts and workflow.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Support</title>
      <link>https://kgilmer.github.io/r13-dev-site/docs/policy-and-process/support/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kgilmer.github.io/r13-dev-site/docs/policy-and-process/support/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
